Mitsudomoe EP#3 Translation
Episode title: you and your pervertism.
Your father has it rough doesn't he!
Whats with my papa?
Nothing to mention. So after you look like an 18 years old looking girl, what do you want to do?
I thought of buying ecchi books and giving them to Chiba as presents.
Why?
I can't take the panty shots in the manga anymore!
He was very sad looking...
He is being sympathized by Futaba.
I understand the situation, but you can't buy them.
Well give the ones that you have and well be all right.
I don't have them! Your art is good, so why don't you just draw some bare pictures and give it to him?
Brilliant!
Now... I will create an Ero book.
I don't have any part in this.
You are the editor in chief.
How does it look? Erotic? Are you getting excited?
No way.
How can it be!
Shin chan wont get excited over my nude body!
Why you...
Is it not impossible if it is Futaba?
No not that, I am talking about the art.
But it has nothing but nudity...It would be good if you put some underwears on them.
As expected from Shin-chan, you have grown to the point of being an Ero consultant.
You have grown haven't you!
Crap...why did I give off such a lame advise?
I've done nothing but naked arts, so Im bad with underwears.
Just look at a pair while you draw.
Oh, right!
Hold it!
Here?
She's not wearing any!
Not looking, not looking...
How thoughtless of me...
Well, Shin-chan...
Which one do you like??
Wha-What...
Pick a pair!
W-well then T-These...
Futaba
I won.
This is the only bra which Micchan never uses.
Then why'd she buy it at any rate?
Well then...
What're you doing?!
Thats because I can draw it more correctly if I have a model infront of me.
Where is Sanjo, where did Sanjo go away to?!
The panties too!
Help me...
Don't move.
Damn it, I feel like there is something that is broken and making a noise inside me. This is just too much thinking that I am doing all these embarrassing things for Chiba.
What is taking her so long...
Done!
OH YEAH!
Well, Does it makes you excited?
Yes, It makes me excited.
Hooray! He says he is excited!
Not again... This is the worst!!
It's finally complete isn't it?
It's a masterpiece.
Though I lost a lot of precious something...
Ah! Chiba-chi!
I'll give you ero-book.
What?! Thank you!
What is this Just pictures?
I'm more of a magazine liking guy.
But Shin-chan said drawings were more exciting...
I guess we'r on a different level.
Well now, Let's see if anyone threw away their magazines around the river bank!
Yes sir!
Mitsudomoe!
L-Let's do the problems on page 123.
Isn't Yabecchi a bit weird today?
He is.
You think so? I don't pay much attention to him, I can't really tell the difference.
It is an Earthquake!*
Earthquake earthquake earthquake!
Yabecchi's gone nutz! Someone call an ambulance!
It's an evacuation drill!
Oh, okay...
You should've told us!
There's no point if I say, "We're going to practice evacuating" upfront!
Now everyone use up your imaginations! Earthquake!
Everyone hide under their desks!
I don't belong under a desk.
Yes you're dead. You have just died!
If you don't take refuge under your desk like this way, you could be stabbed right through  the head by flying shards of glass, or fall and hit your head and die. Noe that is a tragedy
Don't just kill me off like that! Beside Yabecchi hasn't hidden under the desk as of yet.
I see, I see.
[Dead tired]
[Just a while ago]
Hitoha-chan, why were you under here during class?!
Doesn't that makes under the desk more dangearous?
Things like this happen as well, but the dead just keep silence will you!
Dead...
The earthquake has caused a fire from the 3rd floor home economics room.
Next is a fire!
What's with that pattern?
It's made from my sister's leftover fabric.
As though there is no tension at all.
Yabecchi, Micchan isn't here you know.
Go on ahead!
I'm a corpse now, how do you expect me tomove? Carry me!
About 80kg total
Come on now the fire is narrowing down the exit!
Almost there.
KAKAKABOOM!
Uh oh, the ceiling collapsed and blocked the exit!
That's what you get for  dragging your feet!
The smoke's getting thicker!
Gotta cover my mouth...
Everyone else got out just fine, what is taking Yabe-sensei so long?
Kuriyama-sensei!
Yabe-sensei's committing sex crimes in the fire!
Wait, lend me a hand!
You're trapped in a sea of flames now. What're you gonna do?
I can't take it no more...
It is ok if you just Ditched the corpse!
You were awake?!
You're a corpse too!
I'm just an injured.
You were pretty dead to me!
Be it Injured or corpse...I'm your teacher and you're my treasured students.
Eww.
Necro.
But what do I do?
It's hot...so hot...
Mitsuba-chan's sweating like rain up there...
Sweat! That's it!
Mitsuba-chan, get down!
Huh? Whatever.
It's out, the fire's out!
S-Stop, my panties!
There must be some sort of mistake.
Yes, I'm sure my imagination just ran away with me.
My panties!
Thank goodness...we put out the fire.
Ugh...
Yabe-sensei, you panty-obsessed sicko!
Wha-Wait, no! She's dead!
So your finally 'cracked'...
Hello? I need an ambulance.
N-No!
It's all just a drill!
Mitsudomoe
In a corner of otherwise lively Sports-meet, there was a single father battling with loneliness.
I've looked everywhere and I can't find Daddy at any place!
Then he did not come. Give it up.
But...
Maybe he's in the building?
You can't go in there!
We've gotten word there's an intruder inside the school building.
He's here.
He's here!
Maybe...it's your fath-
No!
Tell everyone that when they catch him they need to put him under maximum security!
Of course...
But it could be your fathe...
It's not him. Please tell everyone to put him under strict guard after capturing him.
Well that is obvious...
It might be papa...
You are wrong, treating papa like a common criminal. You should be ashamed of yourself.
You just don't wanna do the parent-child three-legged race.
It couldn't be...any less meaningless.
Well, try your best to not COMPLETELY humiliate yourself.
I wanna do the three-legged race with daddy!
Papa is going to die then
I gotta go find a set of clothes.
You see him?
Nope, he's not here.
Let's try over that way.
I wonder why everyone sees him as being an intruder so easily, anyway...
If he's wearing regular clothes and acting normally, he should not be under suspicion.
Hey, hey! Wait, Hitoha!
What happened to your trousers??
It all happened so fast...
I was practicing for the three-legged race with a chair...
Good.
I can't untie it...
I'll just have to take my pants off real quick.
What the hell are you doing you bastard?!
So I was running here and there-
I get it.
Just you practicing with a chair is embarrassing enough...
But as your father isn't this an important duty for me!
But we don't have to do it if you don't want...
...It's okay...
R-Really?
All right! I'm so happy!
D-Don't be so loud!
Is someone else in here?
All right! I'm so happy!
,,She talks to herself!
Okay, we're short on time. Pull me out!
Let's get to the starting line, pronto!
I quit, I quit!
Next up is the parent-child three-legged race.
It's starting!
One two, one two...
Hey, stop!
Hold on!
That's her father!
Yeah right! There's no resemblance at all!
Look closer please...look at the reckless intensity on their faces.
And more than that, they're breathing is perfectly in sync!
Wh-What the hell is with that clothing?!
Micchan, your dad's so serious...he's kinda cool!
No way!
Isn't he?
Goal!
Get him!
No, no, he's my f...
I-I don't know this man!
Hitoha-chan, calm down.
No...we had such a good time running... Yhr bond of father and child...
Lock him up, please!
Mitsudomoe...!
Ouch!
What was that for?
It's finally complete...
My new super move is ready!
Super move?
My "Lightspeed One-Handed Panty Snatch" ended in a bad result.
But now I have the "Lightspeed One-Handed Bra Liberator!"
Nothing bad will happen if I use it on a guy by accident!
You live a fun life, huh?
What's your new move?
I bet it's just a skirt-flip or something stupid.
Don't judge things you have no Idea on!
Then hit me with your best shot.
Me too, me too!
No can do.
None of you have br-...the right to face my moves!
W-What's that supposed to mean?!
Hey, pants-pervert Satou! What's kinda move is he talking about?
It's, uh...hey, I'm not a pervert!
Crap...now that I think about it, almost none of the girls wear bras!
You idiot, you're too smart for your own good!
I had made  bought a new bra yesterday.
It's a French design.
How wonderful!
Hey.
Can you not take on my secret move?
Wait a second, how come Sugisaki's good enough and I'm not?
What secret move? Forget it, I don't wanna know.
Please! There's no one else! It's gotta be you! It won't work if it isn't you! Your the only one for it!
Could he be...
What's so great about this weird pants girl?
Same goes for you...
I don't want to! Your move's probably just lifting up my skirt or something like that!
You're worthy of my super move because you have a br...  you posses an object.
I understand, it's money isn't it! Money's the only thing that this girls got!
Why do you so much desperate?
It's a love-hate triangle relationship!
This side has 'snapped' as well!
Good luck, Chiba-kun!
Don't get involved, you'll just make things worse.
I'll help out as well!!
Help?!
Is she wearing a bra too?
Can you take on my super new move?
Hey, I thought I was the only one!
So Yoshioka, you're the kind of girl who'd steal her friend's man!
That's not what I meant!
Forget them, lick my feet! Now!
I don't know anything.
My first bra unhooking...I want it to be special...who do I pick?
Of course...I've got two hands, don't I?
Huh?
Chiba-kun?
Where'd he go?
Lightspeed TWO-HANDED Bra...
What?
Oh no!
We have swimming next period!
I knew you were gonna flip my skirt, you gorilla pig!
This would've happened even if you'd succeeded.
Mitsu...domoe...
Your father used to be pretty popular back in those days.
Well, you can't go back in time.
I like the way you are now papa!!
You girls would have fought for my attention all the time.
I love you Daddy!
Me too Daddy!
Don't make things up so much!
It's all true.
I'll kiss you enough for all three of us!
Ow, ow, don't tear up my beard...
And don't eat it.
Oh yeah, I've got people coming over today.
And you're an eyesore, so go in the other room and don't come out!
People? Friends of yours?
They're not my friends!
Coming in!
Hey!
Let's do our presentation fast and get out of here.
Where's your dad and Futaba?
Out.
Aww, I wanted to meet your dad Micchan...
You don't need to meet him!
Huh?
I'm nothing like him!
He's fat, loud, and totally annoying!
But then you're just like him, from head to toe!
Shut up, shut up!
Stop it!
Come on, please don't fight!
Just get the homework done and get out of here!
You have to do it too!
I'm in charge here, you have to follow my orders!
Micchan, who is this cool person?!
Whoa.
Is he a model?
Whats your relation with him?
Uhh...well...you know...
We've got a verrrrry close relationship!
Y-Y-You mean you're d-dating?
He and I are forever linked by a strong bond .
Wow, Micchan!
Technically, I'm not lying.
And his name? What's his name?
S...Soujirou.
So cool!
Have you ever...chuued him? [TL NOTE: chuu in colliq Japanese means kiss]
Of course!
You lie!
It's all true!
Well then show me some proof will you! Call him and well see.
N-No way! He's a busy man!
I knew you were lying.
All right, all right!
It's from the next room...
Hello?
W-What's up?
Mitsuba?
He said "Mitsuba!"
Say, "Soujirou, I love you!"
What's she doing?
Say it! Say "I love you!"
If you can't say it that proves you were lying!
I, uh...
Sou-
Soujirou...
I LOVE YOU!
Satisfied?!
It can't be...
I love him more!
You idiot!
Futaba-chan's involved too?
We take a bath together every night,sometimes I even sleep with him!
B-Baths?
Sleeping together?!
Incomprehensible
I love him more than you and Hitoha put together!
Sanjo too?!
I love all three of you!
S-Shut up!
Look at you three, still fighting over your old dad...
C'mere so I can give you all a big hug!
I don't particularly care for you.
I love him the most!  Me, me me!
...What about our preparation for the presentation?
{Mitsudodmoe ED LandSelling//
End of ED//}
The way Yabecchi risked his life to protect Micchan and Sanjo was so heroic,but  Micchan and
Sugi-chan are in a love triangle with Chiba-kun,
but actually Micchan has someone she's in love with, and Futaba-chan loves him too!
Episode 4 - Beautiful Drama
Is that how you saw it all?
Shin-chan!
What is that creature on your chest?
Do I look like an 18 year old?
18 years? No way!
You're lying! Even though these boobs are very big!
Its not the problem of how big it is.
Even thoug these are so soft!
It doesn't matters even if it is soft!
I finally received this from Santa-san this X-mas.